





Software Development Senior Analyst seeking roles in Application Development, Requirement Gathering, Solution Architecture, Service Delivery Excellence. Change

Management, Agile, Scrum, Waterfall, Java, Python, IntelliJ, Eclipse, Soap UI, SQL Developer, Mongo DB.

Current Designation: Software Development Senior Analyst - Java

ouvu

Current Company: NTT DATA GLOBAL DELIVERY SERVICES PRIVATE LIMITED

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore
Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore,Mysore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Tech Lead, Application Development, Requirement Gathering, Solution Architecture, Service Delivery Excellence, Change Management, Agile, Scrum, Java, Python, IntelliJ, Edipse, Mongo DB, Spring, Hibernate, Spring

Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [INFORMATION

Notice Period: 2 Months

SCIENCE

Boot,MySQL,JUnit,JWT,Rest

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Performance driven IT professional with an analytical bent of mind offering 5.5 years of experience in spearheading all aspects of Software Development Lifecycle across multiple domains

Notable success in managing multiple activities starting from understanding customer requirements, identifying the right technology stack, deriving the right solution, feasibility study, implementation, process stabilization, performance monitoring, key metrics development, resource deployment, stakeholder reporting, solution planning, architectural design, evaluation & solution implementation, scalability, risk assessment & mitigation, migration & transformation and supporting after go-live for Web Based software applications (SOAP and REST services)

Work Experience

NTT DATA GLOBAL DELIVERY SERVICES PRIVATE LIMITED as Software Development Senior Analyst -Java Mar 2019 to Till Date

Project Executed: Project Title: DMP (Data Management Platform) Client Name: Tokio Marine Kiln (TMK) Technologies Used: Python 3.6, Flask, SQL Alchemy, Postgress, JWT, Celery, Flask Restplus, Numpy and Pandas

Robert Bosch Engineering and Business Solution as Senior Engineer Jul 2018 to Feb 2019

Project Executed: Project Title: CATS - CAP ALM Ticketing System Client Name: RBEI Technologies Used: Java 8, Spring Boot, JPA, Mcroservices, No SQL, MongoDB, Rabbit MQ

Evry India Pvt. Ltd., as Senior Software Engineer Aug 2015 to Jul 2018

Project Executed: Project Title: Cards- Accounts and Cards Evolution (ACE) Client Name: EVRY UK Technologies Used: Java1.8, JPA2, Spring 4.0, Lombok 1.16, Jetty 9, Maven 3, CXF 3, SLF4J 1.7, Junit 4, Mockito 1.10, Orika 1.4 +

^ Back to Top



Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Education

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
IntelliJ, Edipse, SoapUl			
SQL developer, Mongo DB			
MySQL, PG Admin			
JAVA, PYTHON			
Apache CXF, Spring, Hibernate			
Junit, DBunit, Mockito, Jetty			
Spring Boot, MongoDB, Rabbit MQ			
NoSQL, JDBC, JPA, XML, XSD's			
Flask, SQL Alchemy, JWT			
Celery, Flask Restplus, Numpy and Pandas			
Jenkins			
Apache Tomcat, Docker, WinScp			
MAVEN			
FITNESSE			
GIT, SVN, RTC, Bit Bucket			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Kannada				
Tulu				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.